export const ELEMENTS = [
    '💫', '🔮', '🌈', '✨', '🎉', '🦄', '🌟', '💥', '🔥', '💎',
    '🍀', '🧠', '🍭', '🍕', '🐾', '🎶', '💣', '👑', '🕹️', '👻',
    '🐱', '🐶', '🐢', '🦋', '🐉', '🐧', '🐙', '🦁', '🐝', '🦓',
    '🌻', '🌵', '🌳', '🍁', '🍂', '💐', '🌾', '🍄', '🌴', '🌊',
    '🎈', '🍩', '🍪', '🛸', '🎩', '🪄', '🛍️', '⛵', '🎭', '🚀',
    '⚪', '⚫', '🔷', '🔶', '🔲', '🔳', '🔸', '🔹', '♦', '☀️'
];

export const CURSOR_STYLES = ['default', 'pointer', 'text', 'wait', 'crosshair', 'help'];


export const EASY_QS = [
    { question: '5 + 3', answer: 8 },
    { question: '9 - 4', answer: 5 },
    { question: '7 + 2', answer: 9 },
    { question: '3 * 3', answer: 9 },
    { question: '6 / 2', answer: 3 },
    { question: '8 + 1', answer: 9 },
    { question: '12 - 3', answer: 9 },
    { question: '4 + 4', answer: 8 },
    { question: '2 * 5', answer: 10 },
    { question: '10 - 7', answer: 3 },
];

export const MEDIUM_QS = [
    { question: '12 * 7', answer: 84 },
    { question: '56 / 8', answer: 7 },
    { question: '125 + 80', answer: 205 },
    { question: '45 * 3', answer: 135 },
    { question: '67 - 39', answer: 28 },
    { question: '16 * 9', answer: 144 },
    { question: '150 / 5', answer: 30 },
    { question: '250 + 150', answer: 400 },
    { question: '72 / 9', answer: 8 },
    { question: '180 / 6', answer: 30 },
];

export const HARD_QS = [
    { question: '127 * 128', answer: 16256 },
    { question: '3 * x + 5 = 16', answer: 3.67 },
    { question: '234^2', answer: 54756 },
    { question: '4567 / 89', answer: 51.33 },
    { question: '5 * y - 3 = 42', answer: 9 },
    { question: '√232144', answer: 482.02 },
    { question: '54321 / 1234', answer: 44.03 },
    { question: '15!', answer: 1307674368000 },
    { question: '19^3', answer: 6859 },
    { question: '2 * z + 6 = 100', answer: 47 },
    { question: '3600 / 37', answer: 97.3 },
    { question: '302 * 406', answer: 122412 },
    { question: '1111^5', answer: 1610510001 },
    { question: '7 * x - 4 = 10 * x + 1', answer: -5 },
    { question: '149 * 998', answer: 148502 },
    { question: '18^4', answer: 104976 },
    { question: '987654321 / 123456', answer: 8000.06 },
    { question: '123^4', answer: 228886641 },
    { question: '99999^2', answer: 9999800001 },
    { question: '4 * x + 5 = 2 * x + 9', answer: 2 },
    { question: '750 * 896', answer: 672000 },
    { question: '44444 / 1111', answer: 40 },
    { question: '350 * 450', answer: 157500 },
    { question: '12345 / 25', answer: 493.8 },
    { question: '3 * y + 15 = 66', answer: 17 },
    { question: '80^3', answer: 512000 },
    { question: '∛512000', answer: 80 },
    { question: '256^2', answer: 65536 },
    { question: '5 * x + 20 = 50', answer: 6 },
    { question: '111 * 987', answer: 109857 },
    { question: '89756 / 453', answer: 198.25 },
    { question: '100^5', answer: 10000000000 },
];